whiterose.ac.uk 2019-04-26

# Your Privacy - White Rose University Consortium

## Your Privacy

### Collection of Personal Information

We do not capture or store personally-identifying information (such as your e-mail address, name, title or postal address) without your knowledge when you visit our site. Personally-identifying information can only be collected on our website if you choose to provide it. In the case of a specific enquiry, we reply to the enquiry and do not keep your details on file unless specifically requested to do so.  
If you wish to receive other information relating to the White Rose Consortium please state clearly in your correspondence. We may then use your details to contact you with current and future information about our work, events and activities.  
However, you will always have the opportunity to opt out of receiving further information. To do this please send an e-mail to [info@whiterose.ac.uk](mailto:info@whiterose.ac.uk "info@whiterose.ac.uk") with the following subject line: ‘Remove’ and include your name and address so that we can identify your records for removal.  
In order to modify your personal data the subject line should state ‘Modify Personal Data’ – please include your modifications in the body of the e-mail.

### Security

This site has security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control.

### Changes

We may without notice change, modify or withdraw access to this site.

### Contacting the Web Site

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web Site, you can contact [info@whiterose.ac.uk](mailto:info@whiterose.ac.uk)

* * *

## Who we are

Our website address is: http://www.whiterose.ac.uk.

## What personal data we collect and why we collect it

### Comments

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymised string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Contact forms

### Cookies

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information and your screen display choices. Login cookies last for two days, and screen options cookies last for a year. If you select “Remember Me”, your login will persist for two weeks. If you log out of your account, the login cookies will be removed.

If you edit or publish an article, an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the article you just edited. It expires after 1 day.

### Embedded content from other websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

## Who we share your data with

## How long we retain your data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognise and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What rights you have over your data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

## Where we send your data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

## Your contact information

## Additional information

### How we protect your data

### What data breach procedures we have in place

### What third parties we receive data from

### What automated decision making and/or profiling we do with user data

### Industry regulatory disclosure requirements
